





Full Stack Web Developer

WHO AM I?

Python developer, with knowledge of APIs, mainly with Django Rest. Regular knowledge of Angular, with Bootstrap and Tailwind. I helped companies build web applications for e-commerce with more than 1 million users, knowledge of ERP functionalities and biotechnology software.

I have good adaptability in knowledge of business rules. I have great knowledge in SQL databases. In all the applications I worked on, agile methodologies such as Scrum, Kanban and Poker Planning were applied.

Python / Django / Git / REST APIs / Confluence / Jira / Google Cloud Platform (GCP) / Linux / SQL / Agile Methodologies / TypeScript / Angular

LANGUAGES

Português - Native

Inglês - Advanced / Technician

EXPERIENCE

2022-01 - Current Full Stack Web Developer

Neoprospecta

Back-End Developer Django / Django Rest Framework with TDD and Unit Testing in software for biotechnology solutions. Development of features and maintenance in Angular.

Bitbucket / Confluence / Jira / Web Crawling / Google Cloud Platform (GCP) / Linux / PostgreSQL / Agile Methodologies / REST APIs / Python / Django REST Framework / TypeScript / Django / Bootstrap / AngularJS / Angular

2022-10 - 2023-10 **Backend Web Developer**

Atar B2B

Back-End Developer Django / Django Rest Framework with TDD and Unit Testing in software for biotechnology solutions. Development of features and maintenance in Angular.

Github / Confluence / Jira / Web Crawling / Google Cloud Platform (GCP) / Linux / Docker / Agile Methodologies / REST APIs / Python / Architecture / AngularJS / FastAPI

2019-08 - 2022-01 Full Stack Web Developer

Magazine Médica

Full Stack Web Developer Python / Django / JS / Firebird / PostgreSQL - E-commerce / Internal System Develop APIs, Front-End, Back-End with tests in TDD, Database Modeling, UX/UI and Data Analysis.

Bitbucket / Jira / Firebase / Financial Analysis / PostgreSQL / REST APIs / User Experience (UX) / Python / Django / Bootstrap / JavaScript

2018-11 - 2019-08 Database Analyst and Support

IXCSoft

SQL database migrations with DBs from external telecommunications systems to own system. Maintenance in MySQL to ERP database.

Analytical Skills / Microsoft SQL Server / PostgreSQL / Strategic Planning / Customer Service / SQL / MySQL / Firebird

2018-01 - 2018-11 Full Stack Web Developer Internship

Federal University of Fronteira Sul

Full Stack Web Python/Plone Developer - Institutional Site.
Plone / NoSQL / Python / Bootstrap / HTML5

EDUCATION

2015 - 2018 Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

UFFS - Federal University of Fronteira Sul

Graduate

2019 – 2020 **Systems Analysis, Design and Management**

UNOPAR College

Postgraduate

2020 - 2021	Software Engineering Postgraduate	FAEL College
2020 - 2021	UX Design e Learning Experience Postgraduate	Instructional Design Institute
2021 - 2021	Cloud Computing Projects Postgraduate	Descomplica college
2021 - 2021	LGPD Postgraduate	Legale College
2022 - 2023	Technologies for Professional Education Postgraduate	IFSC - Federal Institute of Santa Catarina
2023 - 2024	DevOps Engineering Pós-Graduação	Focus College
2021 – 2021	Accounting Technical Education	FASPEC